Mhm.
>> Welcome to
January 15th, 2026 Board of Adjustments
meeting. Uh clerk, can you please call
roll?
>> Curtis Claybaugh.
Charity Campfield.
>> Here.
>> Linda Burt.
Dustin Brown.
>> Here.
>> Michael O'Donnell.
>> Erin LeBlanc.
>> Here.
>> Chair, you have a quorum.
>> Thank you.
All right, our first order of business
is election of officers for 2026 term.
Oh, yeah, absolutely. Let's uh we'll
start with introductions.
Um we can start Are you all right if we
start here on my left?
>> Uh good evening. My name is Mike
O'Donnell. I'm
a retired city attorney among other
things and happy to serve on the board.
>> Uh good evening. I'm Dustin Brown. I've
been with the Board of Adjustments here
for a few years and um
glad to be here.
>> My name is Jeffrey Bolt. I am a contract
attorney for the board. I'm an attorney
in private practice.
Um I'm not a city employee.
>> I'm Erin LeBlanc and I've been on the
board
I don't know, three, four years
um
and I work at the Laramie County Senior
Center.
>> I'm Charity Campfield. I'm the newest
member of the board. My day job, I am a
town administrator, clerk, treasurer.
Um so
hopefully I can bring some experience to
the board.
>> Charity.
>> Yeah, welcome.
All right. Can I Can I ask you guys to
introduce as well or we can just All
right.
>> I'm Erin Figan. I'm a planner for the um
Planning and Development Office and I um
help organize the Board of Adjustment.
>> Charles Blue, Planning and Development
Director. I've been here for just over 7
years.
Uh wear multiple hats. I sometimes feel
like I have nine different uh
directions I go in any given day.
>> I'm Morgan Dennis. I'm a planner in the
Planning Department.
>> All right. Thank you, everyone. All
right. And then going to our first order
of business, election of officers for
the 2026 term. And we have the chair,
the vice chair, and the secretary.
>> Mr. Chairman, I have a question. Would
you accept a
nominated slate as opposed to doing the
elections individually?
>> Uh we did that last year. Is there any
concern if we do that again this year?
>> Chair, members of of the board, no,
there isn't a concern. The only
item is it's technically my secret
ballot, so
we'll just pass a
piece of paper.
We have papers, so you'll just mark yes
or no on that, and we won't know who did
anything.
>> But the nominations are public.
>> Correct. Nominations are public. The
slate for the vote will be is private.
>> Private. Got it.
Well, then if you're ready,
>> Mhm.
>> Mr. Chairman, I have a
slate of officers to propose by way of a
motion.
Uh I nominate yourself, Dustin Brown,
for chair,
Linda Burt for the vice chair, and
Charity Campfield as secretary.
>> Thank you, sir.
>> Do you need a second on that motion?
>> Charles, yeah.
>> I'll second.
>> And then we fill out our
ballots. Is that correct?
>> Chair, for you, yes, you'll um
mark those on write the names on your
ballot, and then mark
who you would like to vote for.
Is there any other nominations?
All right.
>> Easy enough.
>> And Mr. Chair, while that's going
around, I just got a text from my wife
that the Zoom is getting the circle of
death. That it's not accessible.
She probably has the old one. I'll tell
her when I get home.
>> [laughter]
>> Mr. Chair, the votes have been tallied
and the slate has been approved.
>> Thank you.
Okay. Moving into our next item of
business is the approval of minutes for
December 18th, 2025.
Um the chair will entertain a motion.
>> Mr. Chair.
Unless somebody else wants to go ahead,
Aaron.
No.
Okay.
Uh oh, wait. Do we need to have to read
the report the the item first into the
record before I move?
>> So, um we're at the approval of the
minutes from December.
>> You said that and I didn't hear it. I'm
>> No, you're great.
>> Move to approve the minutes.
>> I'll second.
>> Any discussion?
All right. All in favor of approving the
minutes, say aye.
>> Aye.
>> All opposed, say aye.
All right. With that, the minutes are
minutes are approved.
And staff, can you please read in the
item A, the first order of business for
us tonight?
>> Item A, a request PUDC-25-270
conditional use request to allow general
industrial within the LI zone.
Located at lot 14, block two, Swan Ranch
Rail Park, 11th filing, um Clear Creek
way.
The agent is Troy Spreker, and the case
planner is Morgan Dennis.
>> Thank you.
And uh can we have the staff report on
the item as well?
>> Mr. Chair
Mr. Chair, board,
um Morgan Dennis, planning and
development.
This is a conditional use to allow
general industrial within an LI zone
district.
The property is legally described as lot
14, block two of Swan Ranch Rail Park,
11th filing.
The property is surrounded by LI zoning
to the north and south. To the west of
the
parcel is the Swan Ranch Rail Park PUD,
which is a planned unit development for
industrial land use.
To the east of the parcel and across
Clear Creek Parkway are parcels zoned
for CB.
The proposed
project plan to develop
project is to develop a shipping and
courier service facility. The property
is indicated as mixed use employment
within Plan Cheyenne, which emphasize a
range of commercial or light industrial
development that should not be located
near residential development.
The proposed use of grant of general
general industrial would be in character
for the area. The operating
characteristics would be complementary
to the surrounding area.
Current developments on nearby developed
properties have light industrial or
general industrial uses.
Clear Creek Parkway allows for direct
access to Interstate 25, which keeps
large vehicle traffic away from public
and shared roads. The routes in this
area have been identified as part of the
freight network within Connect 2025.
If this conditional use is approved, a
site plan application will be needed to
be submitted for the project.
Due to the meeting due to meeting all
review criteria, staff recommend
approval.
>> Thank you. Any questions for our staff
member?
Thank you very much.
Is there anyone here representing the
project that would like to speak? Please
come forward.
State your name and your address for the
board, please.
>> Hello. My name is Troy Spreker.
Uh my uh I'm with Lamp Rynearson. Our
address is 4715 Innovation Drive, Fort
Collins. And I'm here representing
the project.
>> Thank you. Do you swear to tell the
truth on the matter before the Board of
Adjustment this evening?
>> Yes.
>> All right, please proceed.
>> Okay. Um
So, yeah, I think uh Morgan covered the
project pretty well. Um I know there's
really not a lot more that I could say
other than it's going to be a a nice
facility. There's not a lot going on out
there. Traffic is going to be pretty
minimal uh
overall within the area. Um
Trucks and with trailers will be
entering, but it'll be really in the
early mornings and they're going to be
more in the later afternoons or evenings
when
probably two trucks would come in, two
trucks would leave, two trucks would
come in, two trucks would leave. So,
there's really not a lot of traffic that
we're anticipating
uh throughout the day. It's going to be
more
uh vans, uh cars,
um people coming in to visit the site to
pick up their packages, and then leaving
the site. So,
in our minds, it's going to be a pretty
a low intense as intensity as far as an
industrial use.
Um and it's
an I zone district and it's going to be
centrally located.
And I know I was had uh the items one
through eight to go through and I can
either just go through or you could ask
me questions, which
would be my preference.
>> No, that's that's great, sir. Thank you.
Um and with that, um members of the
board, any questions for the applicant?
>> Mr. Chairman, I think there's one
important question. Who is your
companion tonight?
>> Oh, this is my lovely daughter. So,
>> [laughter]
>> I have brought her to several of these
meetings and
um
she is
here hanging out learning about uh how
all of this works.
>> Think we ought to just welcome her.
>> Yeah.
It's awesome to have her.
>> All right. That's great. All right. Um
with no further questions, we'll open up
uh public comment as well on this item.
Is there anyone here to speak for the
public? Maybe online?
All right. With that, we'll go ahead and
close public comment. Is there
um any comment before we go ahead and
call roll on this item?
Oh, absolutely. Sorry. Um at this point,
the chair would entertain a motion.
>> I move to approve a conditional use
request for the use of general
industrial at lot 14, block two, Swan
Ranch Rail Park, 11th filing as
presented by the applicant as the
application meets all review criteria
outlined in the UDC section 2.2.4.B.
>> Thank you. And with that, do we have a
second?
>> Second.
>> Thank you.
And uh please call roll.
>> Charity Campfield?
Dustin Brown?
>> Yes.
>> Michael O'Donnell?
>> Aye.
>> Aaron LeBlanc?
>> Yes.
>> Chair the action passes.
>> All right, thank you.
And with that, we are on to other
business and staff announcements. Um
with that, I'll turn it over to um our
staff.
>> And to your members of the board, um
next meeting,
it'll be the middle of the legislative
session, so that'll be be fun. We'll all
be exhausted. So, it should be good.
Um but, we do have items planned for
next meeting. And the next meeting, we
do expect to have uh more members here,
and we do intend to do our planning
commission 101 train or board of
adjustment 101 training. We have so many
different boards and commissions that we
do our training every year. So, we'll go
ahead and do that. That'll uh just be a
general overview of what your roles are,
your responsibilities, and a little bit
of discussion on
on quorum and ex parte communications
and the uh Wyoming uh
uh meetings act, open meetings act.
So, with that, I don't have
anything Oh, and I I guess I should note
that last Wednesday, Connor White, a
planner two in our department, he
frequented here um before.
Um he mailed out our last public notice
letters
for our 2022 council uh
county pocket annexation.
>> Oh, that's great news.
>> So, we do anticipate to have all of the
county pockets annexed uh by the middle
of March. Uh right now, we're moving
forward with the annexation of the Cole
property.
Um that's section 20, north of the mall.
We have an agreement with the property
owners there um on that one. It should
really relieve them of
concerns with development in multiple
jurisdictions, and also the Edwards
Development Company up north as well. Um
and we have two other properties. One's
the school district and the city fire
station site. So, moving forward with
that, and then our last one will be down
south, picking up a couple of remnants
and some on Westland Road.
>> Thank you, sir.
>> Yeah, great. Uh please go ahead, sir.
>> Thank you, Mr. Chairman. Generals, how
long should we plan on the meeting next
month?
Do you have a sense?
>> Mr. Chairman of the board, um we only
have one item that's proposed, and I've
pledged to really reduce the time of the
101s. The preservation board one was
about 6 minutes
uh last time. I've really just I've just
deleted half the slides. So, it's pretty
good.
Um I should know uh our unified
development code annual review, that
actually closed up uh for collection of
public comments last Friday.
Uh what we intend to do is we're
presenting the concerns we've heard from
the public, from electeds,
uh just from our experience, and from
the planning commission. We're
presenting them to the city council to
work session next Friday, the 23rd at
noon in this room.
And then we will be
holding a work session with the planning
commission on the third Tuesday
of February,
which is February 17th,
um to set an action plan for what
amendments we may move forward with uh
for the unified development code.
So, right now I think everything's
fitting pretty well because we had zero
variances in calendar year 2025.
>> Thank you. Any other comments? Any other
discussion?
Ma'am, can I ask you to come gavel us
out?
Interested?
I'm on I'm on 6 years of this. We got to
do something fun.
>> [laughter]
>> It'd be great.
What's your name again, Ms.
Here you go.
And all you got to do is say the meeting
is adjourned and hit the gavel.
>> Meeting is adjourned.
>> All right. Way to go. Thank you.
>> Well done.
>> [laughter]